[ Music ]
[音乐]
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Hello, everyone.
&gt;&gt; 嗨 大家
Good afternoon.
大家下午好
Welcome to the session.
欢迎大家来到这次会议
My name is Tao.
我是 Tao
I'm from Core ML Team.
我来自 Core ML 团队
Today we're super excited to
今天我们十分激动
talk about a few new features we
能够来讨论我们今年
added to Create ML this year.
在 Create ML 中添加的一些新功能
In What's New in Machine
在机器学习讨论会的
Learning Session, you were
新内容中 你们了解了
introduced to the brand-new
全新的 Create ML App
It's a great new tool designed
这是 Apple 设计的
by Apple to guide you through
一款出色的新工具
the essential steps of training
它可指导你完成
of machine learning models.
机器学习模型培训的基本步骤
We believe this makes your
我们相信这会使
machine learning workflow easy
你们的机器学习工作流程
and approachable.
变得简单易用
Now, let's start with Text
现在 让我们
Classification.
从文本分类开始
What is Text Classification?
什么是文本分类
It's a machine learning task
这是一个机器学习的任务
that classifies input text to a
它将文本分类为
set of predefined labels.
一组预定义标签
You can use it for sentiment
你可以将其用于情感分析
analysis, like classifying text
例如将文本分类为
as positive or negative.
正面或负面
Or doing spam detection.
或者做垃圾邮件检测
Or more complicated things like
或者更复杂的事情
topic analysis, classifying text
如主题分析 将文本分类为
as food, politics, or science.
食物类 政治类或科学类
Now, Text Classification has
好 自去年以来
been supported since last year,
文本分类一直被推崇
but this year we're adding the
但我们今年正在增加
support for the state of the art
对艺术迁移学习状态的支持
Today, I'm going to give you a
今天 我将向你们
concrete example of how you can
具体举例说明
train a Text Classifier using
如何使用迁移学习
Transfer Learning.
训练文本分类器
To train such a model, the first
要训练这样的一个模型
thing you'll want to do is
你要做的第一件事
collect some training data.
就是收集一些训练数据
Once you have the data, you can
一旦获得数据后
organize in an easy way.
你们便可以轻松地进行整理
I have sports, entertainment and
我这儿有运动类 娱乐类和自然类
Under each folder, I have a few
在每个文件夹下
text files.
我有一些文本文件
And each one of them is a single
而且他们中的每一个都是
training example, and its label
一个训练样例
is simply the name of the folder
它们的标签就是
they are in.
它们所在文件夹的名称
And that's it.
就是这样
That's all you need to do with
这就是你们要对这些数据
the data.
做的所有处理
I'll give you a quick demo to
我会给你们一个快速演示
show how you can do this.
告诉你们如何做到这一点
On my desktop, I have a training
在我的桌面上
data folder.
我有一个训练数据的文件夹
So, I decided to have a little
那么 我决定找点乐子
Instead of using plain text as
我没有使用纯文本作为标签
the label, I used a few emojis.
而是使用了一些表情符号
For example, for entertainment I
例如 对于娱乐类我使用
use a camcorder.
一个摄像机图标
For sport, I'm using an American
对于运动类 我用了一个橄榄球
For nature, I'm using this cute
对于自然类
little tent besides a great pine
我则用了一个可爱的小帐篷
tree.
旁边有棵大松树
You notice there is also this
你注意那儿还有
other folder.
这个其他文件夹
This is the training data that I
这其实是我不想要的
actually don't want.
训练数据
I want my model to learn such
我希望我的模型能够学习
that anything that's not one of
任何不属于
the three intended class, I want
以上三个目标类的东西
my model to classify them into
我希望我的模型将它们
this class.
分到这个类中
So, let's take a look at a few
那么 我们来看看
examples here.
这里的一些例子
For example if you read this
例如 如果你们读了
sentence, there's something
这个句子 有一些关于
about writer and IMDB.
作家和 IMDB 的东西
It's clearly something related
这显然与
to entertainment.
娱乐有关
If I go into other folder, this
如果我进入其他文件夹
is not one of the three intended
它不是以上三个类中的一个
That's about data.
这是关于数据的问题
Now, I'll go to Create ML app.
现在 我要进入 Create ML App
To do that, I go to Developer
为此 我转到开发人员工具中
Tools and find the Create ML.
并找到 Create ML
But I'm going to do a new
然而我要做一个新文件
document and go to text.
然后转去文本
I'll name it like that.
我会这样命名它
Create. So, I'm sure you have
创建 好的 我相信你们
seen this user interface in the
已经在早期的会议中
earlier session, Object
看到了这个用户界面
Connection and
对象连接和子分类
So, I'm just going to drag my
所以 我在这里就
training data in directly here.
直接拖动我的训练数据
So, it gives you some feedback
所以它会为你们提供一些
about your training data.
有关你们训练数据的反馈
But what's new about Text
但是文本分类器的新功能是
Classifier is this particular
这个特殊的参数部分
So, for today's demo, I'm going
所以 对于今天的演示
to select Transfer Learning.
我将选择迁移学习
If we take a look at it, the
如果我们看看它的话就知道
first two algorithms actually
自去年以来
have been supported since last
实际上前两种算法
year.
已经被鼓励使用了
And this year we're adding
那么今年我们正在
Transfer Learning.
添加迁移学习
And for the demo I'm going to
对于演示 我将
use this feature extractor
使用名为 Dynamic Embedding 的
called Dynamic Embedding.
此功能提取器
I'll go into the detail about
我将在稍后的演示之后
what is Transfer Learning a bit
详细介绍
later after the demo, but all
什么是迁移学习
you need to know now is Transfer
但现在你需要知道的
Learning with Dynamic Embedding
是用 Dynamic Embedding 进行的迁移学习
is actually an algorithm that
它实际上是一种
pays attention to the semantic
注重输入文本的
meaning of your input text.
语义含义的算法
I'll start training.
我要开始训练数据了
So, in general, Transfer
因此 一般来说
Learning takes a bit longer to
迁移学习需要更长的时间来训练
For this particular data set,
对于这个特定的数据集
it'll take about five minutes on
在这台特定的机器上
this particular machine.
大约需要五分钟
So, I'm not going to wait.
好了 我不会干等着
Instead, I have my pre-picked
相反 我在这里预先选择的
solution here that's trained on
解决方案是在完全相同的数据上
exactly the same data.
进行训练的
Once the model has been trained,
模型一旦经过训练后
the accuracy test gives you a
精度测试可以很好地
good summary about how your
总结你的模型
model performs on different
对不同的数据执行情况如何
data, broken down into different
分解为不同的类做得如何
It looks my model has done a
看起来我的模型
good job on training validation
在训练验证和测试数据方面
and testing data.
做得很好
So, I will directly jump to the
所以 我将直接跳转到
output tab.
输出选项卡
This preview pane gives you some
此预览窗格给你提供了
summary about the model as well
有关模型的一些总结
as a few different ways for you
以及一些快速实验的
to do some quick experiments.
不同方法
For example, if you go to the
例如 如果你转到右下角
you can directly add File to do
则可以直接添加 File
a quick test.
以进行快速测试
Or you can track a folder that
或者 你可以跟踪
the model will be able to make
模型能够预测该文件夹中
prediction of all the text file
所有文本文件的文件夹
The model actually will use the
该模型实际上
entire body of the text in each
将使用每个文件中的
file to make a single
整个文本来进行
prediction.
单个预测
But there is another way for you
但是还有另一种方法
to do quick experiment which is
可以让你进行快速实验
manually typing.
即手动输入
So in this particular text input
因此 在这个特定的文本输入部分
section, when you, when I type
当你 当我键入每个空格时
each space, or if I stop typing
或者如果我
for a little while, the model
停止输入一段时间
will make a prediction.
模型将进行预测
So, let's see how that works.
那么 让我们看看它是如何运作的
What a comeback win.
真是反败为胜啊
Sport. Let's try something
运动类 让我们来试试
different.
不同的东西
The season finale adds a twist
本季结局为情节
to the plot.
增添了一丝转折
Which seems about right.
这似乎刚刚好
Entertainment.
娱乐类 [掌声]
I actually also want to try
我实际上也想尝试
something more recent and more
一些更近期和
relevant.
更相关的东西
This just came to me last night.
我昨晚才想到这件事
The Raptors are on top of the
猛龙是联盟总冠军
Nature [laughter].
自然类 [笑声]
Well, if I switch context.
好吧 如果我切换语境的话
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
It predicts sport.
它也可以预测运动类
So, I'm pretty happy with the
好了 我对模型的表现
model performance.
非常满意
Now I'm ready to deploy.
现在我准备好进行布置
So, I just simply drag it out
所以 我只需将其拖出来
and I can put it on my iOS
我就可以把它放在
devices.
我的 iOS 设备上
That's how you can train a Text
这就是你如何使用
Classifier using Transfer
迁移学习训练
Learning.
文本分类器
But you might want to ask what
但你们可能想问
is Transfer Learning?
什么是迁移学习
Transfer Learning is a powerful
迁移学习是一种功能强大的
machine learning technique where
机器学习技术
a model trained on a huge amount
这其中针对一个特定任务的
of data for one particular task
大量数据训练模型
can be repurposed for another
可以被重新用于另一个任务
task so that you, as developers,
因此你们作为开发人员
only need to prepare limited
只需要准备有限数目的数据
amount of data and still get
并同样可以获得
your customized machine learning
个性化的机器学习模型
Create ML actually uses Transfer
Create ML 如今实际上使用
Learning for image
迁移学习来进行
classification today.
图像分类
And now we're bringing it to
现在我们将它带到文本中
Well, to train a good Transfer
那么 要为文本训练
Learning model for text, the
一个好的迁移学习模型
problem is a little bit
问题就有点不同了
If you read this sentence, "I
如果你们读到这句话
was able to park my car near the
“我能把车停在公园入口附近”
For a model that's trained with
对于一个使用传统技术
conventional technique or study
或研究嵌入
embedding, these two parts will
进行训练的模型
look exactly the same.
这两个部分看起来是完全相同的
But for a model trained with
但是对于一个使用 Dynamic Embedding
Transfer Learning with Dynamic
的迁移学习训练的模型
Embedding, because it pays
因为它注重
attention to the semantic
整个上下文的
meaning of the overall context,
语义含义
it is able to figure out these
所以它能够弄清楚
two parts actually mean
这两个部分实际上意味着
different things.
不同的事物
To train such a good model, you
要训练这样好的一个模型
need to do it on many texts.
你需要在很多文本上训练
That's exactly what we did.
这正是我们所做的
We trained on billions of text
我们对数十亿文本进行了训练
and shipped that pretrained
并将这种预先训练的模型
model to your mobile devices.
发送到你们的移动设备上去
And more importantly, we
更重要的是
optimized its performance so
我们优化了其性能
that you only need to prepare
因此你们只需准备
your limited amount of raw text,
有限数量的原始文本
send it in to Create ML app.
将其发送到 Create ML App 上
Underneath it, it'll interact
在它深处 它将与
with the model that's already
已经是你们 OS 中
part of your OS and gives your
一部分的模型进行交互
customized text classifier.
并提供自定义文本分类器
And you can deploy the same
而且 你们可以在 iOS 设备上
model on your iOS devices
无缝地部署
seamlessly because the
相同的模型 因为
pretrained model is already
预训练模型
there for you to use.
已经可供你们使用
Now, that's the workflow to use
好了 这就是使用 Create ML App
the Create ML app to train your
训练文本分类器的
Text Classifier.
工作流程
If you're also interested in
如果你也想编写代码
writing code, it's also very
那同样会很容易
To use the Transfer Learning
要使用带 Dynamic Embedding 的
with Dynamic Embedding, the only
迁移学习
thing you need to specify is
你唯一需要指定的是
this model parameter.
此模型参数
The rest of the code is exactly
其余代码
the same as last year.
与去年完全相同
Now, I've shown you how to train
现在 我已经向你们展示了
Text Classifier, but I'd like to
如何训练文本分类器
give you a few simple tips to
但我还想给你们一些简单的提示
get the most out of your Text
以便充分利用你们的文本分类器
Now, choose an algorithm which
现在 选择适合
suits your use case.
你们所用例子的算法
Transfer Learning is only one of
迁移学习
the three algorithms that Text
只是文本分类器支持的
Classifier supports.
三种算法之一
Different algorithms have
不同的算法有
different tradeoffs.
不同的侧重点
To find out which one fits your
要找出哪一个最适合
use case best, please go to the
你的所选例子
Natural Language session that
请看看这之后举行的
happens after this.
Natural Language 会议
Provide balanced classes.
提供均衡的分类
This is very important.
这是非常重要的
In the particular example that I
在我向你们展示的特定示例中
showed you, because each text
因为每个文本文件
file is a single training
都是一个训练示例
So, I roughly kept the same
所以 我大致在每个文件夹中
amount of text files in each of
保留了相同数量的文本文件
Data consistency.
数据一致性
If you expect your Text
如果你希望你的文本分类器
Classifier to mostly work on
主要用于短句
short sentences, like I do, your
就像我一样
training data should be mostly
你的训练数据应该
consisting of such examples.
主要由这些示例组成
If you expect your Text
如果你希望你的文本分类器
Classifier to work on short
能够处理
words, paragraphs, or even an
几句话 段落 甚至整篇文章
entire article, you also want to
你也需要确保
make sure your training data
你的训练数据
cover these cases as well.
同样包括这些例子
[ Applause ]
[掌声]